Jerald Baroro

Web Developer

Goal-oriented Web Developer brings strong commitment to collaboration and solutions-oriented problem-solving. Use various web design packages to develop custom-crafted, customer-focused websites and designs. Committed to high standards of user experience, usability and speed. Lends detailed knowledge of Node and React Web Development, and Javascript programming.

Work History

2021-03 -

JavaScript Developer

Panteum Foundation, Singapore, Cebu City, Cebu Creating and building a CSS Framework dynamically using Javascript, SASS/SCSS, PugJS, and NodeJS. Designed the elements of CSS framework and also maintaining and constantly improving its layout and design and showcasing all the CSS components.

2019-11 -2021-01

Process Executive

Cognizant Philippines, Cebu City, Cebu

- Answered telephone or online requests and completed interactions quickly to meet productivity goals.
- Collaborated with team to define business requirements for organizational processes, achieve productivity standards and adhere to accuracy standards.

2019-07 -2021-10

Customer Service Representative

Teleperformance IT Park, Cebu City, Cebu

- Achieved and consistently exceeded revenue quota through product and service promotion during routine calls.
- Offered advice and assistance to customers, paying attention to special needs or wants.
- Responded to customer requests for products, services and company information.

Education

2017-06 -

Associate of Science: Information Technology

Siquijor State College - Lazi Campus - Tigbawan, Lazi, Siquijor

2008-06 -

High School Diploma

2012-04 Lazi National Agricultural School - Tigbawan, Lazi,

Siquijor

2011-06 -2012-04

Computer Hardware Servicing NC II: Computer Hardware Servicing

Lazi National Agricultural School - Tigbawan, Lazi, Siquijor

Certifications

2020-10 The Complete 2020 Web Development Bootcamp

2020-11 Advanced CSS and Sass: Flexbox, Grid, Animations

and More!

2020-12 Node with React: Fullstack Web Development

References

Thomas M A - CEO at Panteum, linkedin.com/in/m-thomas-sys

Ralph Villanueva - JS Team Lead,

linkedin.com/in/ralph-villanueva-44ba80185

Contact

Address

Cebu City, CEB, 6000

Phone

09667652125

E-mail

spaueOfficial@gmail.com

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/jeraldbaroro-562aab20

www

github.com/jeralddevOfficial

www

jerald-dev.herokuapp.com/

Skills

HTML5

Excellent

JavaScript



CSS3



C Programming



ReactJS



MongoDB



NodeJS



Photoshop



Tailwindcss



PugJS



ExpressJS



Restful API



SASS



Visual Studio Code



Chess

